http://www.hotyogaofkirkland.com/privacy-policy/

hotyogaofkirkland.com This domain is expired. Please renew.
Web Site Privacy Policy
Overview
Thank you for visiting hotyogaofkirkland.com (the "Web Site") and reviewing our Privacy Policy. Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information
about you when you visit the Web Site unless you choose to provide that information. This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or
from the Web Site.
What Type of Information We Collect
The server on which the Web Site is located collects and saves only the default information customarily logged by web server software. Such information may include the date and time of your visit, the
originating IP address, and the pages and images requested.
The Web Site and third party advertisers may use cookies and other technologies such as web beacons to keep track of the web searches you make while visiting this website, as well as your web surfing
behavior on this website and other websites you may visit to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use The Web Site in order to improve the quality of our services or serve appropriate
advertising. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. If you would like to know more about these practices and your choices
about not having this information used to target ads to you, please click here. Cookies used by the Web Site may store
user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly
without cookies.
In some cases, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number)
about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Uses
We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.
We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services.
We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of The Web Site.
When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and
services.
The Web Site processes personal information on servers in the United States of America. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country.
hotyogaofkirkland.com - This Domain registered at Directnic.
Privacy Policy
